flash-game-design.com 2019-01-26

# Privacy Policy – FlashGameDesign

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and services.

**What Information Do We Collect?  **  
When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

**Personal Information You Choose to Provide  **  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.  
**  
Web Site Use Information  **  
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called “web beacons” or “clear gifs” to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

**What Are Cookies?  **  
A cookie is a small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**Ad Servers**  
To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

**Sharing Information with Third Parties  **  
We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

**Google Ads  **  
– Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

– Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.

– You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy .

– We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here .

**Your Consent  **  
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Flash Game Design. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You can choose to opt-out from such information collection and use, including a clear link to the NAI’s opt-out page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp .

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact Flash Game Design.
